[{"answer": "Weekly or monthly", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Why do you think you tell me, my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I understand", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Don't tell me, 'cause I'm not going to tell you what I've got", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I have a lot of money. Do you know how much money I've got", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I've got three big ones", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Tastes good", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What do you think's wrong with her", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Maybe... but you're the one whose ass is dragging", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Is she against you getting help", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "It doesn't matter how I feel about it. It's how you feel about it that matters", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You didn't come to me because you have a rich imagination", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "an investigator for the that place", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Sounds like you have several", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You know how easy it is. A kid can manage it if he wants a fake I.D. You can do practically the whole deal at your local that place. The only variable is how much pride you take in the product", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "All new people start with that..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You're doing great", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "It doesn't matter. Go on", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What happened today", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Was it something that happened at school", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " I don't even know why han", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "My approach", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Finally, some common sense..", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I think you know what I mean", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I think you know what I mean", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I think you do", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "No, I really don't", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Why don't you tell me", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "...I mean, my friend, the dude is seriously deluded. I said that to him, I said,", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " He said ", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It might've been more appropriate if we had followed a traditional approach to the docto", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yes, something's very wrong, Dr. my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What was that", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Transference", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Doc..", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I want to give you something. Will you let me", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Yes, you do, you damn well do", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I'm sorry you're frustrated", "docId": "Mumford.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "No, sir. I was empathizing. Sorry", "qsentId": 40}]